opportunitiesforafricans.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy Policy | Opportunities For Africans

This Privacy Policy sets out the policy for use of this website [www.opportunitiesforafricans.com](http://www.opportunitiesforafricans.com/) (OFA). We respect the privacy rights of users of this website and recognise the importance of protecting your personal information.

OFA is a site which helps to spread opportunities for the convenience of Africans and this is done based on available information at the time of publication. OFA will use its best endeavors to publish accurate information on accessible opportunities, however we shall not be liable for any unintended or inaccurate information. It is recommended that visitors to OFA visit the site of the opportunity provider.

The opportunities on OFA are shared solely for the purpose of disseminating information to the public and shall not be associated with any other purposes.

OFA is committed to safeguarding the privacy of your information at all times. This Privacy Policy explains how we use the information we collect about you and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

**What information do we collect**?

We collect information from you when you register on our mailing list. When registering on the website, you may be asked to enter details which include your name and e-mail address.

**What do we use your information for?**

We may use the information we collect from you in any of the following ways:

  * to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our Terms of Use; and
  * to send periodic emails regarding the available opportunities on OFA.

**How do we protect your information?**

At OFA, we implement a variety of reasonable security measures to protect the security and integrity of your personal information.

We use computer safeguard such as firewalls and data encryption, and files and only authorise access to personal information to only employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities or our affiliates as may be required for the smooth running of the website.

However, as the internet is not a fully secured medium, and we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur accordingly we are not responsible for the matters, which include actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties that breach our reasonable security procedure.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not share your personally identifiable information with unauthorized third parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating the website, conducting our business as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce the website policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Third Party Links

Usually, our website contains links to websites owned and operated by third parties, these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and we urge you to review them – because this Privacy Policy will not apply. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content, activities and privacy practices of such third party websites.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This blog does not use cookies. However, some of our business partners, for example, advertisers may use cookies and web beacons when they advertise on OFA, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google AdSense) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases whether you have flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

**Your Consent**

By submitting any personal information to us, you consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy** ** **

We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy and if we do, we will post the changes on this page. It is your responsibility to check the Privacy Policy every time you submit information to us. Your use will signify that you agree to any such changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us [info@opportunitiesforafricans.com](mailto:info@opportunitiesforafricans.com) or[ opportunitiesforafricans.com@gmail.com](mailto:opportunitiesforafricans.com@gmail.com)
